accesshydroponic.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy statement - Your Company Name

Your name, address, phone number, other personal information and your credit card number are not stored on the Internet with our system. Once you provide your information, it is instantly sent, encrypted, directly to our order processing system, which is on a server separate from the Internet. 

The personal information we may collect is used by us to respond to your inquiry, process an order, send you a newsletter that you have subscribed or allow you to access specific account information. Accesstattoo.com may also use any personal information provided by you to measure the use of our site and to improve its content. 

At times cookies may be used to help us serve you better. A cookie is a tiny element of data sent by a web site to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and, if you wish, to reject it. 

**Secure Site**  
We use 128-bit encryption Secured Socket Layer (SSL) for secure transmissions provided by COMODO. Your shopping with us is guaranteed safe from the time you enter all your personal information up to the time you pay for your order. 

**How do you check that a page you're in is secure?**  
Verify the URL (address). If you're on a secure page, it should start with https" indicates it is secure, example: [https://www.accesshydroponic.com ](https://www.accesshydroponic.com/). A padlock image also should appear at the bottom of your browser window. Information exchanged with any address beginning with https is encrypted using SSL before transmission. If you're not on a secure page, it starts with http:// with no "s", example: [http://www. accesshydroponic.com ](http://www.%20accesshydroponic.com/). The page is secured once you start your ordering process by signing in. 

**Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)**  
While SSL protects your data "in transit" , PCI DSS protects your < "stored data" (i.e., your personal info, username, password).

**What is Payment Card Industry (PCI) Compliance?**  
The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Program is a mandated security initiative, which was created to offer merchants and service providers a complete, unified approach to safeguarding credit cardholder information for all card brands. 

In September of 2006, a group of five leading payment brands including American Express, Discover Financial Services, JCB, MasterCard Worldwide and Visa International jointly announced formation of the PCI Security Standards Council, an independent council established to manage ongoing evolution of the PCI standard. Concurrent with the announcement, the council released version 1.1 of the PCI standard. 

**What Are the PCI Compliance Standards?**  
The PCI Data Security Standard requirements apply to all payment card network members, merchants and service providers that store, process or transmit cardholder data, and affect all payment channels, these include all entities which store, process, or transmit cardholder data must be PCI compliant. Payment channels including retail (brick and mortar), mail/telephone order, and e-commerce organizations.

The PCI Data Security Standard represents a common set of industry tools and measurements to help ensure the safe handling of sensitive information. Initially created by aligning Visa's Account Information Security (AIS)/Cardholder Information Security (CISP) programs with MasterCard's Site Data Protection (SDP) program, the standard provides an actionable framework for developing a robust account data security process - including preventing, detecting and reacting to security incidents.<

The updated version, version 1.1, developed by the founding members of the PCI Security Standards Council, became effective with the launch of the PCI Security Standards Council The PCI Data Security Standard is a multifaceted security standard that includes requirements for security management, policies, procedures, network architecture, software design and other critical protective measures. 

**PCI Data Security Standard is comprised of 12 general requirements designed to:**
